Guide to the Ron Kolm Papers, 1970-2016 MSS.079
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Correspondence
  - Stauffer, Jill, undated (Box 2, Folder 121)
  - Stefan-Cole, Janyce, undated (Box 2, Folder 122)
  - Stettner, Irving, undated (Box 2, Folder 123)
  - Strausbaugh, John, undated (Box 2, Folder 124)
  - Strickland, Stephanie, undated (Box 2, Folder 125)
  - Sukenick, Ron, undated (Box 2, Folder 126)
  - Susler, Betsy, undated (Box 2, Folder 127)
  - Swanberg, Ingrid, undated (Box 2, Folder 128)
  - Swezey, Ken, undated (Box 2, Folder 129)
  - Taylor, Cathy, undated (Box 2, Folder 130)
  - Taylor, Claude, undated (Box 2, Folder 131)
  - Teags, Debi, undated (Box 2, Folder 132)
  - Thornton, Thomas, undated (Box 2, Folder 133)
  - Tillman, Lynne, undated (Box 2, Folder 134)
  - Tilson, Charlotte, undated (Box 2, Folder 135)
  - Tilson, Jake, undated (Box 2, Folder 136)
  - Tisa, Ken, undated (Box 2, Folder 137)
  - Tobin, Juanita, undated (Box 2, Folder 138)
  - Topp, Mike, undated (Box 2, Folder 139)
  - Trask, Jason, undated (Box 2, Folder 140)
  - Ulin, David, undated (Box 2, Folder 141)
  - Underwood, John, undated (Box 2, Folder 142)
  - Urdang, Stephanie, undated (Box 2, Folder 143)
  - Versace, Nathan, undated (Box 2, Folder 144)
  - Violi, Paul, undated (Box 2, Folder 145)
  - Vitale, Alfred, undated (Box 2, Folder 146)
  - Waldman, Anne, undated (Box 2, Folder 147)
  - Warshawski, Morrie, undated (Box 2, Folder 148)
  - Watson, Carl, undated (Box 2, Folder 149)
  - Weber, Ben, undated (Box 2, Folder 150)
  - Weber, Bruce, undated (Box 2, Folder 151)
  - Wellman, Jerry, undated (Box 2, Folder 152)
  - Whittemore, Reed, undated (Box 2, Folder 153)
  - Wierzbicki, Carol, undated (Box 2, Folder 154)
  - Williams, Gary, undated (Box 2, Folder 155)
  - Williams, Jonathan, undated (Box 2, Folder 156)
  - Wilmarth, Richard, undated (Box 2, Folder 157)
  - Wilmott, Anne, undated (Box 2, Folder 158)
  - Wilson, Blair, undated (Box 2, Folder 159)
  - Wilson, Peter Lamborn, undated (Box 2, Folder 160)
  - Wingate, Steve, undated (Box 2, Folder 161)
  - Wittig, Bob, undated (Box 2, Folder 162)
  - Witz, Bob, undated (Box 2, Folder 163)
  - Wortsman, Peter, undated (Box 2, Folder 164)
  - Wright, Jeff, undated (Box 2, Folder 165)
  - Yourgrau, Barry, undated (Box 2, Folder 166)
  - Zarco, Cyn, undated (Box 2, Folder 167)
  - Zavatsky, Bill, undated (Box 2, Folder 168)
  - Zelevansky, Paul, undated (Box 2, Folder 169)
  - Zodd, undated (Box 2, Folder 170)
  - Zukofsky, Paul, undated (Box 2, Folder 171)
  - Zummer, Tom, undated (Box 2, Folder 172)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, undated (Box 2, Folder 173)
- Series II: Manuscripts
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains manuscripts sent to Ron Kolm as a friend or as an editor. Included are many manuscript drafts by downtown writers.
  This series is arranged alphabetically by author.
  - Ahern, Tom--Manuscript Material for 5+5, undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Anderson, Holly--Lilly Lou, undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Alexander, Lynn, undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Andrucyk, Inez--"I've sold out.", undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Andrucyk, Inez--Blind Devotion, undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Anthony, William -- Artwork, undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Bey, Hakim--What Is Moorish Anarchy?, undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Blagg, Max--Beaker Of Lightning, undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Blagg, Max--Bohemian Veneer, undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Blagg, Max--Bolham Butts, undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Blagg, Max--The Bump, undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Blagg, Max--Dad, undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Blagg, Max--Drinks And Towns In Notts & Yorks, undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Blagg, Max--Five Days, undated (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Blagg, Max-- Forgive Me Hollywood, undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Blagg, Max--Fresh Welts, undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Blagg, Max--Gush, undated (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Blagg, Max--It's Time, undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Blagg, Max--Last Of London, undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Blagg, Max--Maracas, undated (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Blagg, Max--Monkey Wrench In The Garden Of Allah, undated (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Blagg, Max-- The Origins of Dance, undated (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Blagg, Max--Poldrick's Little Secret, undated (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Blagg, Max--3 Locations/Notations From The Trek, undated (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Blagg, Max--What Remains, undated (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Burroughs, William--Some Considerations On The Paperback Publication of The Necronomicon, undated (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Carter, Michael--Artist's Call, undated (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Carter, Michael--Nigredo, undated (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Carter, Michael--20 Years, undated (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Cherches, Peter--The Music Critic And The Soprano, undated (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Deyab, Larry--Artwork, undated (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Duhamel, Denise--Why The Gap Should Have Picked Me Instead Of Max Blagg For It's Television Poetry Commercial, undated (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Eidus, Janice--The Mail, undated (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Eidus, Janice--The Marriage Breakfast, undated (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Eidus, Janice--Out Of The Schoolyard, undated (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Feast, Jim-- Authors Intros (Part XIII a-c), undated (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Feast, Jim-- Autonomedia Proposal, undated (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Feast, Jim--Beat Seminar Chronology, undated (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Feast, Jim--Chagunas, undated (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Feast, Jim--Chants For Seance, undated (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Feast, Jim--Con Lady and the Unknown Gangster, undated (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Feast, Jim--Day Of Infamy, undated (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Feast, Jim--Guns & Gonads: A Secret History of the O.J. Jury, undated (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Feast, Jim -- Lundi, Vendredi, undated (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Feast, Jim--Madison/Pulaski, undated (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Feast, Jim--Ming Sing, undated (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Feast, Jim--One Size Fits All Party Platform, undated (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Feast, Jim--On Pataphysics, undated (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Feast, Jim--Untitled, undated (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Feast, Jim--Vowel, undated (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Filzman, Norman--The Catering Wall, undated (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Fishberg, Lawrence--First Person, undated (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Fishberg, Lawrence--The Rubber Room, undated (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Golden, Mike--A Downtown State Of Mind, undated (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Golden, Mike--Pitch This, undated (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Golden, Mike--Please Don't Squeeze The Shaman, undated (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Golden, Mike--Rope Dancing In Little Egypt, undated (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Golden, Mike -- Miscellaneous Manuscripts, undated (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Golden, Mike--Without Daring, undated (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Hageman, Leita--Poems, undated (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Heine, Dean--The Frog Poem, undated (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Halgren, Will--To The Tune Of Miss Lulu Had A Steamboat, undated (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Hamill, Juan--The Big Sleep, undated (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Hardin, Rob-- Erased Mistress, undated (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Hardin, Rob--Evolution, undated (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Hardin, Rob--First Draft, undated (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Hardin, Rob--Hugo Wolf, undated (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Hardin, Rob--Inquiry, undated (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Hardin, Rob--Mood Music, undated (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Hardin, Rob--Senryu, undated (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Hardin, Rob--Tomomania (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Holman, Bob--Epithalamium, undated (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Holman, Bob--Fire: Friend Or Foe?, undated (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Holman, Bob--For Jorge Brandon, undated (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Holman, Bob--If I Were To Throw My Money, undated (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Holman, Bob--Not For Lack Of Understanding, undated (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Huberman, David--Bacon And Blintzes, undated (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Huberman, David--Call Me Killer, undated (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - Huberman, David--Fat Boy, undated (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - Huberman, David--The Grind, undated (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - Huberman, David--Hard-up, Hard-on, Limp Dick (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - Huberman, David--Life Sentence, undated (Box 3, Folder 82)
  - Huberman, David--Nuclear Age Boy, undated (Box 3, Folder 83)
  - Huberman, David--Psycho T.V. Shows, undated (Box 3, Folder 84)
  - Huberman, David--She's The One, undated (Box 3, Folder 85)
  - Huberman, David--Talk About It, undated (Box 3, Folder 86)
  - Huberman, David--Word Man, undated (Box 3, Folder 87)
  - Kasper, Michael--Words With Pictures, undated (Box 3, Folder 88)
  - Kolm, Ron/TZ--Beach Party, undated (Box 3, Folder 89)
  - Kolm, Ron--Death In Koln, undated (Box 3, Folder 90)
  - Kolm, Ron--Fronts, undated (Box 3, Folder 91)
  - Kolm, Ron--In The Silence Between Bombs, undated (Box 3, Folder 92)
  - Kolm, Ron/Zummer, Tom--Duke & Jill Postmodernism Parody, undated (Box 3, Folder 93)
  - Kolm, Ron--Make Love, Not War, undated (Box 3, Folder 94)
  - Kolm, Ron--Meet Me At Mao's, undated (Box 3, Folder 95)
  - Kolm, Ron--My Father, undated (Box 3, Folder 96)
  - Kolm, Ron--The Scholar, undated (Box 3, Folder 97)
  - Kolm, Ron--Suburban Ambush, undated (Box 3, Folder 98)
  - Kolm, Ron--Swimming At The Shallow End Of The Pool, undated (Box 3, Folder 99)
  - Kolm, Ron--The Vision, undated (Box 3, Folder 100)
  - Kostelanetz, Richard--The Literature Of Soho, undated (Box 3, Folder 101)
  - Kostelanetz, Richard--Blowing The College Teaching Biz, undated (Box 3, Folder 102)
  - Kupferberg, Tuli--Manuscripts, undated (Box 3, Folder 103)
  - Kruth, John--"probably bob", undated (Box 3, Folder 104)
  - Kruth, John--The Mysterious History Of Manhattan, undated (Box 3, Folder 105)
  - LaBombarda, Michael--Plays, undated (Box 3, Folder 106)
  - LaBombarda, Michael--Poetry, undated (Box 3, Folder 107)
  - LaBombarda, Michael--Prose, undated (Box 3, Folder 108)
  - Leary, Mary--Trash Can Trolls, undated (Box 3, Folder 109)
  - Leary, Mary--Who In The Hell Is Frandon Freels?, undated (Box 3, Folder 110)
  - Leary, Mary--Miscellaneous Manuscripts, undated (Box 3, Folder 111)
  - Litzsky Tsaurah-Fallout Follies, undated (Box 3, Folder 112)
  - Litzsky Tsaurah--Sex, Sex, Sex, undated (Box 3, Folder 113)
  - Litzsky, Tsaurah--The End Of The World, undated (Box 3, Folder 114)
  - Litzsky, Tsaurah--Three Poems, undated (Box 3, Folder 115)
  - Mathews, Harry and others--"Oulipo" material, undated (Box 3, Folder 116)
  - Maynard, Joe--Clancy's (Box 3, Folder 117)
  - Maynard, Joe--Manuscripts, undated (Box 3, Folder 118)
  - McGlynn, Bob--N, undated (Box 3, Folder 119)
  - Myles, Eileen--December, undated (Box 3, Folder 120)
  - Nostrand, Jennifer--Untitled Poetry Manuscripts, undated (Box 3, Folder 121)
  - Ochiishi--In From The Dream, undated (Box 3, Folder 122)
  - Padua, Jose--Manuscripts, undated (Box 3, Folder 123)
  - Plantenga, Bart--Barbie & Her Perilous Anatomy, undated (Box 3, Folder 124)
  - Plantenga, Bart--The Beer Mystic's Shadow, undated (Box 3, Folder 125)
  - Plantenga, Bart--Big Nouns, Unconjugated Verbs, undated (Box 3, Folder 126)
  - Plantenga, Bart--Beliefs In The Material Progress, undated (Box 3, Folder 127)
  - Plantenga, Bart--Cold Crackpot Life, undated (Box 3, Folder 128)
  - Plantenga, Bart--Confessions Of A Beer Mystic, undated (Box 3, Folder 129)
  - Plantenga, Bart--Enchanting Bonbons, undated (Box 3, Folder 130)
  - Plantenga, Bart--Fellow De Se, undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Plantenga, Bart--Floating Flowers, undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Plantenga, Bart--Fun=Disney+Balanced Checkbook+BMW-Gum Disease, undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Plantenga, Bart--Get Or Be Gotten, undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Plantenga, Bart--Hitler's Dog, undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Plantenga, Bart--I Don't Feel Like Myself & I Feel Good, undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Plantenga, Bart--Interdiction, undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Plantenga, Bart--Duke & Jill Parody --Duke & Jill Run Out Of Coffee, undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Randall, Michael--Buzzard Hunting Dog, undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Randall, Michael--A Dollar's Worth, undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Randall, Michael--Eight Ball, undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Randall, Michael--Geronimo, undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Randall, Michael--Ice, undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Randall, Michael--Joey, undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Randall, Michael--A Man Wrapped In Plastic, undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Randall, Michael--Maneuvers, undated (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Randall, Michael--October Music, undated (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Randall, Michael-- Sex And Temperament In Three Primitive Societies, undated (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Randall, Michael--Miscellaneous Poems, undated (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Rapaport, Jill--Bellevue, undated (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Rapaport, Jill--Death, undated (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Rapaport, Jill--H.R. Haldeman, 1993, Which Seems To Mean Something (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Rapaport, Jill--Hong Kong Song, undated (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Rapaport, Jill--Panoplistic Traditions In Memphis, undated (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Rapaport, Jill--The Scintillation Of The Soviet Interstice, undated (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Rapaport, Jill--The Weirdness Of The Text, undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Rattray, David--The Butterfly, undated (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Rutkowski, Thad--Manuscripts, undated (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Salasin, Sal--Gary Gilmore--"Nothing to prove", undated (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Savage, Tom--A Good Friday, undated (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Savage, Tom-- Anecdotal Ticket For Saving Lost Souls, undated (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Savage, Tom--The Assassination Of Jesse Helms, undated (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Savage, Tom--Between B & C There's A Piano, undated (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Savage, Tom--"Bunker" poems, undated (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Savage, Tom--Collaborations (w. Bill Kushner & Dean Kostos), undated (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Savage, Tom--Computer Set Up Fantasy, undated (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Savage, Tom--Creating The Whites In Their Eyes, undated (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Savage, Tom--Enemies, undated (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Savage, Tom--First Fidelity, Here's What We See, undated (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Savage, Tom--Hypnagogia, undated (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Savage, Tom--Impatience, undated (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Savage, Tom--"It was such fun having nutmeg over you", undated (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Savage, Tom--July 4, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Savage, Tom--Just Say Ouch, undated (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Savage, Tom--More Noise, undated (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Savage, Tom--Plodding Through Posterity At Fales, undated (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Savage, Tom--Poetry By The Pound?, undated (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Savage, Tom--Prove That I Lie, undated (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Savage, Tom--Selling Books On The Street, undated (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Savage, Tom--Shop Talk At Word Station Twelve, undated (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Savage, Tom--There's No Way Outta Here, undated (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Savage, Tom--Tompkins Square Tree Talk, undated (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Savage, Tom--Train West Of Sardou & Sapho, undated (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Savage, Tom--Unsafe Sex, undated (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Savage, Tom--Wildfires Burn In My Heart, undated (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Schein, Lorraine--Clitoral, or The Ninth Orgasm, undated (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Schein, Lorraine--Sex, undated (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Schiffrin, Anya--Articles, undated (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Scutti, Susan--Economics, undated (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Sirowitz, Hal-- Untitled book-length manuscript, undated (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Sirowitz, Hal--Miscellaneous manuscripts, undated (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Sirowitz, Hal--Collaborations with Blair Wilson, undated (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Sparrow--Manuscripts, undated (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Sparrow--Against Nature, undated (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Sparrow--Appearances manuscript, undated (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Sparrow--Cartoons, undated (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Sparrow--One Size Fits All, undated (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Sparrow--Presidential Campaign, undated (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Taylor, Claude--Manuscripts, undated (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Topp, Mike--Bohemian Rhapsody, undated (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Topp, Mike--The Disappointment, undated (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - Topp, Mike--Red Dust manuscript, undated (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - Topp, Mike--Miscellaneous poems, undated (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - Topp, Mike--Book manuscript (w. poem dedicated to Topp by Paul Violi), undated (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - Ulin, David--Miscellaneous manuscripts, undated (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - Vitale, Alfred--Miscellaneous manuscripts, undated (Box 4, Folder 76)
  - Vitale, Alfred -- Six Sex Poems For An Erotic New York, undated (Box 4, Folder 77)
  - Watson, Carl--Barndance In The Galleries Of Sodom, undated (Box 4, Folder 78)
  - Watson, Carl--Mechanical Humanism, undated (Box 4, Folder 79)
  - Watson, Carl--Modern Love As A Function Of Myth, undated (Box 4, Folder 80)
  - Watson, Carl--Swirling Water In The Brain Causes Madness, undated (Box 4, Folder 81)
  - Wierzbicki, Carol -- Untitled, undated (Box 4, Folder 82)
  - Witz, Bob--"Materials", undated (Box 4, Folder 83)
  - Witz, Bob--Untitled, undated (Box 4, Folder 84)
  - Witz, Bob-- Miscellaneous Manuscripts, undated (Box 4, Folder 85)
  - Zummer, Thomas--(Excerpts from Landscapes), undated (Box 4, Folder 86)
  - Zummer, Thomas--The Library of Secrets, undated (Box 4, Folder 87)
  - Zummer, Thomas--Three Films and Two Optical Devices I Will Never Make, undated (Box 4, Folder 88)
  - Zummer, Thomas--The Unbearable Likeness Of Being, undated (Box 4, Folder 89)
  - Zummer, Thomas--Video Furta Sacra, undated (Box 4, Folder 90)
  - Miscellaneous Manuscripts, undated (Box 4, Folder 91)
- Series III: The Unbearables
  This series contains materials relating to the various events, readings, and periodical publications of The Unbearables; artwork and manuscripts relating to the publication of The Crimes of the Beats; and artwork and manuscripts relating to the publication of Help Yourself.
  - Miscellaneous Unbearables, undated (Box 4, Folder 92)
  - Readings -- Chez Rollo, undated (Box 4, Folder 93)
  - Sparrow Big Fish "Between The Bombs" Event, undated (Box 4, Folder 94)
  - Initiation Proceedings -- No Bar, undated (Box 4, Folder 95)
  - First Crimes Of The Beats Reading At No Bar, undated (Box 4, Folder 96)
  - Unbearables Corpse, undated (Box 4, Folder 97)
  - Reading At Fez Under Time Cafe, undated (Box 4, Folder 98)
  - Second Reading At Fez Under Time Cafe, undated (Box 4, Folder 99)
  - Third Crimes Of The Beats Reading, undated (Box 4, Folder 100)
  - Second NYU Beat Protest, June 1995 (Box 4, Folder 101)
  - Impeachment Proceedings At Eureka Joe's, undated (Box 4, Folder 102)
  - Sophisticated Unbearables Reading, Ward-Nasse, undated (Box 4, Folder 103)
  - Famous Writers Seance, undated (Box 4, Folder 104)
  - Readings --Shandon Star, undated (Box 4, Folder 105)
  - Life Cafe Readings (1st Series), undated (Box 4, Folder 106)
  - Night of 1000 Sponsors, undated (Box 4, Folder 107)
  - At The Poetry Project, undated (Box 4, Folder 108)
  - Endangered Species Reading, undated (Box 4, Folder 109)
  - Digitas, undated (Box 4, Folder 110)
  - Nuyorican Style Reading At Biblio's, undated (Box 4, Folder 111)
  - Miscellaneous Flyers, undated (Box 4, Folder 112)
  - New Yorker Protest #1, undated (Box 4, Folder 113)
  - New Yorker Protest #2, undated (Box 4, Folder 114)
  - First Brooklyn Bridge Reading, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 115)
  - Brooklyn Bridge Reading #2, undated (Box 4, Folder 116)
  - Utopia Reading, undated (Box 4, Folder 117)
  - Deconstructing The University Symposium, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 118)
  - Poetry Game, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 119)
  - Brooklyn Bridge Reading #3, undated (Box 4, Folder 120)
  - Gender Bender Reading, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 121)
  - Borders--Atticus, Computer-linked reading. 1996 (Box 4, Folder 122)
  - Mnemonic City Reading, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 123)
  - Unbearables Assembling Magazine #4, undated (Box 4, Folder 124)
  - Unbearables Assembling Magazine #5, undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Unbearables Portfolio #2, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Unbearables Portfolio #3, undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Photo of Carter, Rapaport, C.X. Hunter and Watson (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Unbearables Corpse. Anarchist Picnic, undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Voices Of Aftershock -- 1990 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Unbearables Money, undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Unbearables Anthology Reviews, undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Response To Beat Protest Criticism, undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Unbearables Anthology Artwork, File #1, undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Unbearables Anthology Artwork File #2, undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Unbearables Anthology materials, undated (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Basinski Review, undated (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Cups Interview by Janice Eidus, undated (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Rollo Whitehead's Health and Whereabouts, undated (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Series IV: Subject Files
  - Subseries A: Writers and Artists
    This subseries contains materials about writers and artists, and includes reviews, clippings, and other miscellaneous printed materials.
    This subseries is arranged alphabetically by the artist's last name.
    - Ackerman(s), undated (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Adams, Jeff, undated (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Alexander, Vicky, undated (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Allen, Roberta, undated (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Anthony, Bill, undated (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Armijo, Richard, undated (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Basquiat, Jean-Michel, undated (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Bauman, Jane (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Benderson, Bruce, undated (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Bennett, Will, undated (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Bevel, Mat, undated (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Blachy, Jimbo, undated (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Blagg, Max, undated (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Blowdryer, Jennifer (Waters), undated (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Bogosian, Eric, undated (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Borkhuis, Charles, undated (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Breuer, Lee, undated (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Brown, Ken, undated (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Brown, Ken, File 2, undated (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Bukowski, Charles, undated (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Burns, Charles, undated (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Cale, David, undated (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Cannon, Steve, undated (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Cardin, Jorga, undated (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Carter, Michael, undated (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Cherches, Peter, undated (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Chung, Nhi (Nancy), undated (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Coe, Sue, undated (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Cohen, Nancy a.k.a. Nancy Koan, undated (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Colby, Todd, undated (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Cole, David, undated (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Coleman, Joe, undated (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - Crumb, Robert, undated (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - Cullman, Brian, undated (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - Daitch, Susan, undated (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - Dali, Salvador, undated (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - Deitch, Kim, undated (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - Desnoyers, Dana, undated (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - Dickson, Jane, undated (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - Drooker, Eric, undated (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - Duhamel, Denise, undated (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - Eberhardt, Isabelle, undated (Box 5, Folder 57)
    - Eidus, Janice, undated (Box 5, Folder 58)
    - Feast, Jim, undated (Box 5, Folder 59)
    - Fishberg, Lawrence, undated (Box 5, Folder 60)
    - Fitzpatrick, Tony, undated (Box 5, Folder 61)
    - Freeman, Dan, undated (Box 5, Folder 62)
    - Friedman, Drew, undated (Box 5, Folder 63)
    - Ginsberg, Allen, undated (Box 5, Folder 64)
    - Giorno, John, undated (Box 5, Folder 65)
    - Golden, Mike, undated (Box 5, Folder 66)
    - Gordon, Mel, undated (Box 5, Folder 67)
    - Gray, Spalding, undated (Box 5, Folder 68)
    - Gunderson, Joanna, undated (Box 5, Folder 69)
    - Hamill, Janet, undated (Box 5, Folder 70)
    - Haring, Keith, undated (Box 5, Folder 71)